## **UCHENNA ENI**

Lekki Gardens 2 Estate, Ajah, Lagos | +234 815 996 9678 | eniuchenna@gmail.com

## **Professional Summary**

A highly motivated young person with a passion for technology and design. Adept knowledge and experience working with popular design software like Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, Canva, Blender as well as object oriented programing languages like C#. Well accustomed to the basic Communication needed to handle coercive relationships with clientele, team members and senior staff.

#### **Soft Skills**

- Communication Skills
- Graphics Designing
- Web Development
- Software Development

- Content Creation
- Digital Marketing
- Technical Writing
- Positive and Professional

### **Professional Skills**

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- Adobe Photoshop & Illustrator

- C#
- Blender
- WordPress
- Bootstrap

## **Experience**

## **Graphics Designer & Web Developer**

JAN 2020 - PRESENT

Freelance - Lagos, Nigeria.

- Create high-quality, creative and visually pleasing 3d & 2d graphics that convey the message and agenda of the client
- Create, Design and Manage Websites for customers.
- Create regular content like fliers, videos and infographics as well as manage social media accounts of customers.

Here's a link to my portfolio to better evaluate my past works: https://yxngdxnny.github.io

## **Product Designer/CNC Router Operator**

MAY 2023 - SEP. 2023

Interstreet LaserCNC Fabrication Factory- Lagos, Nigeria.

- In charge of creating innovative and creative designs in sketches or on the design softwares that are functional and meets the needs of the client.
- Operating the CNC Router to produce design accurately according to the design.
- Supervising workers to ensure superior standards of products.

#### **Business Manager**

SEP 2019 - MAY 2020

Delicios 7even Cakes- Lagos, Nigeria.

- Supervise and manage staffs.
- Ensuring quality and hygiene of goods.
- Ensuring all customers are met with warm reception and are satisfied with each visit.

# **UCHENNA ENI**

Lekki Gardens 2 Estate, Ajah, Lagos | +234 815 996 9678 | eniuchenna@gmail.com

#### **Education & Certifications**

**SSCE** 2013

Topgrade Secondary School- Lagos, Nigeria.

BSC Information Tecchnology

Sikkim Manipal University - Accra Ghana.

2017

#### **Links & Socials**

#### LinkedIn

Check out my linkedin for more professional insights about me: https://www.linkedin.com/in/uchenna-eni-5ba349236/

#### **Github**

Check out my Github to see diverse projects i've participated in: https://github.com/YxngDxnny

#### My Portfolio

Check out my portfolio website, to se my past projects: https://yxngdxnny.github.io